Platform Integrity Verified: PostgreSQL Engine Active.
Operations to perform:
  Apply all migrations: erp
Running pre-migrate handlers for application admin
Running pre-migrate handlers for application auth
Running pre-migrate handlers for application contenttypes
Running pre-migrate handlers for application sessions
Running pre-migrate handlers for application authtoken
Running pre-migrate handlers for application erp
Running pre-migrate handlers for application apps_core
Running migrations:
  Applying erp.0028_remove_taskqueue_source_approval_and_more...
